Guide to the Art Streiber Photographs
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Art Streiber photographs
1984-1994
PC0082
Streiber, Art.
4 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Gift of Art Streiber, 1998
Information about Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of color slides taken by professional photographer Art Streiber, many of which were used in Stanford publications, particularly those of the Department of Athletics. The majority of the images are of football games, players, coaches, and fans. Other sports include tennis, swimming, water polo, gymnastics, baseball, basketball, and track, including a series on track coach Brooks Johnson. Other subjects include the 1987 Cornerstone Weekend events; commencement events of 1985 and 1987; Tom Brokaw's appearance on campus, 1984; orientation events, 1986; and a class held outdoors behind the Quad, 1984.
Collection Contents
- Stanford (Football), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Stadium: Crowd Exterior (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Team: March Entrance (Box 1, Folder 3)
- LSJUMB [Leland Stanford Junior University Marching Band], 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Big Game 84 At Cal (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Football Misc., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Sidelines (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Football Coaches (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Defense, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Offense, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- San Jose State, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Tailgating, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Football Pre-1984 Season (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Stanford Football, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- U. of Arizona, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- UCLA Football, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- USC Football, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Cal Football, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- San Jose State Football, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- U of Texas, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- San Diego State, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Officials, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Locker Room, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Coaches, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Band/Dollie Reunion, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Special Teams, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Tailgating, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Stadium, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Football Team, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Sidelines, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Misc., 1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- LSJUMB, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Defense, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Offense, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Stanford Football, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Team, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Coaches, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Opponents, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- LSJUMB, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Color, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Sidelines, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Injuries/Officials, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Action, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Gator Bowl (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Gator Bowl Stanford Action, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Gator Bowl Clemson Action, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Gator Bowl Clemson Color, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Gator Bowl Stanford Sidelines, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Gator Bowl Stanford Color, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Gator Bowl Gator Bowl Color, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Stanford Football, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- USC, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- San Jose State, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Cal, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- UCLA, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Stanford Football, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Football Misc., 1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Sidelines, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Coaches, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Team, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Fans, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- LSJUMB, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Injuries, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Tailgating, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Defense, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Offense, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- UCLA, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- USC, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- USC, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Swimming/Water Polo, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Misc., 1987 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Cornerstone Weekend Protesters (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Cornerstone Weekend Fireworks (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Cornerstone Weekend Student Performances (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Cornerstone Weekend Over-Alls (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Cornerstone Weekend Speakers (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Cornerstone Weekend: The Crowd (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Cornerstone Weekend: Alumni Dinner (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Graduation (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Orientation (Box 4, Folder 17)
- E50 Class Outdoors (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Graduation, Commencement, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Graduation, Class Day, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Graduation, Baccalaureate, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Tom Brokaw (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Brooks Johnson (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Track Officials (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Stanford Gymnastics, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Men's Volleyball, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Crew (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Men's Golf, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Men's Tennis, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Rossides Women's Tennis (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Eldredge Women's Tennis (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Fendick-Eldridge Doubles (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Misc. Women's Tennis (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Women's Tennis, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Track, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Fendick Women's Tennis (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Werdel Women's Tennis (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Rush, Gretchen (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Kuhlman, Caroline (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Kuhlman D. Rush (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Crew, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Men's Swimming, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Baseball, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Basketball, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Baseball vs. UCLA (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Men's Basketball vs. UCLA, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Baseball Stadium (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Baseball Regional West, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Swimming (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Women's Swimming (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Misc. Sports I (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Misc. Sports II (Box 6, Folder 10)
- USC Football, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Richards Press Box (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Stanford Water Polo (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Stanford Football (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Stanford, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Generic Color Photos, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Stanford Football, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Stanford Football, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Men's Basketball, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Sports Portfolio (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Stanford/Miscellaneous Sports (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Toi Cook (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Stanford/Miscellaneous Scenics (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Stanford Vietnam Veteran's Memorial (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Mario Cuomo (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Graduation, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Axe Committee, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Photographs (Box 9)